

ALPER AKTAŞ
STUDENT

## **CONTACT INFO**

**\** +90 534 621 81 05

contact@aktasalper.com

in /aktasalper/

aktasalper.com

P Buca, İzmir / Turkey

## **EDUCATION**

## **Ege University**

English Language and Literature

2017 - Present

## Küçükçekmece High School

Foreign Language Class **2015** - **2017** 

Çakmaklı Cumhuriyet High School 2013 - 2015

# **LANGUAGES**

Turkish - Native

English - CEFR C1

## **REFERENCES**

# Çağrı Babuçcuoğlu

Software Lead, Front-end Team Lead

1Pixel Digital Agency

cagribabuccuoglu@gmail.com

#### **ABOUT ME**

I am a 23 year old English Language and Literature graduate interested in software development. My entry to software development began with taking online courses on Python and building small projects with it, using various libraries. After I worked as a front-end developer intern, I have been primarily focusing on web development. I am currently working at Etstur as a software development assistant.

#### **EXPERIENCES**

**JUL 25, 2022 - PRESENT** 

Etstur

OCT 2021 - NOV 2021

1Pixel Digital Agency

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT ASSISTANT

Front-end development for Etstur web applications.

FRONT-END DEVELOPER INTERN

Coding functional and responsive sections of pages that correspond to their respective graphical designs, which were provided as issues in Jira Agile development

environment.

Integrating created page sections into Shopify themes to provide customizable and ease to use controls to merchants. In addition to integrating these sections to themes, fetching dynamic store data into page elements using Shopify Liquid templating language.

MAY 2020 - AUG 2021

Freelancer.com

**FREELANCE VIDEO EDITOR** 

Editing & creating advertisement, music and presentation

videos for clients

## **SKILLS & FAMILIARITY**

## **FRONTEND**

- > React
- > TypeScript
- > Vite / webpack
- > Next.js
- > Alpine.js

## **PYTHON**

- > Django
- > Selenium
- > PyQt5
- > Matplotlib

#### **DBMS**

- > MongoDB
- > PostgreSQL
- > SQLite

#### **CERTIFICATES**

React (Basic) HackerRank

10 Apr, 2022

Rest API (Intermediate)

HackerRank

11 Apr, 2022

Python Programming: From Beginner to

Advanced

Bilgi Teknolojileri ve İletişim Kurumu

19 Aug, 2021

SQL (Basic)
HackerRank
12 Aug, 2021